<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.11.0" xml:lang="en-US">
  <compounddef id="md_backend_2node__modules_2send_2_s_e_c_u_r_i_t_y" kind="page">
    <compoundname>md_backend_2node__modules_2send_2_s_e_c_u_r_i_t_y</compoundname>
    <title>Security Policies and Procedures</title>
    <briefdescription>
    </briefdescription>
    <detaileddescription>
<para><anchor id="md_backend_2node__modules_2send_2_s_e_c_u_r_i_t_y_1autotoc_md3166"/> </para>
<sect1 id="md_backend_2node__modules_2send_2_s_e_c_u_r_i_t_y_1autotoc_md3167">
<title>Reporting a Bug</title><para>The <computeroutput>send</computeroutput> team and community take all security bugs seriously. Thank you for improving the security of Express. We appreciate your efforts and responsible disclosure and will make every effort to acknowledge your contributions.</para>
<para>Report security bugs by emailing the current owner(s) of <computeroutput>send</computeroutput>. This information can be found in the npm registry using the command <computeroutput>npm owner ls send</computeroutput>. If unsure or unable to get the information from the above, open an issue in the <ulink url="https://github.com/pillarjs/send/issues">project issue tracker</ulink> asking for the current contact information.</para>
<para>To ensure the timely response to your report, please ensure that the entirety of the report is contained within the email body and not solely behind a web link or an attachment.</para>
<para>At least one owner will acknowledge your email within 48 hours, and will send a more detailed response within 48 hours indicating the next steps in handling your report. After the initial reply to your report, the owners will endeavor to keep you informed of the progress towards a fix and full announcement, and may ask for additional information or guidance. </para>
</sect1>
    </detaileddescription>
    <location file="backend/node_modules/send/SECURITY.md"/>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
