<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.11.0" xml:lang="en-US">
  <compounddef id="md_backend_2node__modules_2node-gyp_2_c_o_n_t_r_i_b_u_t_i_n_g" kind="page">
    <compoundname>md_backend_2node__modules_2node-gyp_2_c_o_n_t_r_i_b_u_t_i_n_g</compoundname>
    <title>Contributing to node-gyp</title>
    <briefdescription>
    </briefdescription>
    <detaileddescription>
<para><anchor id="md_backend_2node__modules_2node-gyp_2_c_o_n_t_r_i_b_u_t_i_n_g_1autotoc_md2389"/> </para>
<sect1 id="md_backend_2node__modules_2node-gyp_2_c_o_n_t_r_i_b_u_t_i_n_g_1autotoc_md2390">
<title>Code of Conduct</title><para>Please read the <ulink url="https://github.com/nodejs/admin/blob/master/CODE_OF_CONDUCT.md">Code of Conduct</ulink> which explains the minimum behavior expectations for node-gyp contributors.</para>
<para><anchor id="md_backend_2node__modules_2node-gyp_2gyp_2_c_o_n_t_r_i_b_u_t_i_n_g_1developers-certificate-of-origin"/> </para>
</sect1>
<sect1 id="md_backend_2node__modules_2node-gyp_2_c_o_n_t_r_i_b_u_t_i_n_g_1autotoc_md2391">
<title>Developer&apos;s Certificate of Origin 1.1</title><para>By making a contribution to this project, I certify that:</para>
<para><itemizedlist>
<listitem><para>(a) The contribution was created in whole or in part by me and I have the right to submit it under the open source license indicated in the file; or</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>(b) The contribution is based upon previous work that, to the best of my knowledge, is covered under an appropriate open source license and I have the right under that license to submit that work with modifications, whether created in whole or in part by me, under the same open source license (unless I am permitted to submit under a different license), as indicated in the file; or</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>(c) The contribution was provided directly to me by some other person who certified (a), (b) or (c) and I have not modified it.</para>
</listitem><listitem><para>(d) I understand and agree that this project and the contribution are public and that a record of the contribution (including all personal information I submit with it, including my sign-off) is maintained indefinitely and may be redistributed consistent with this project or the open source license(s) involved. </para>
</listitem></itemizedlist>
</para>
</sect1>
    </detaileddescription>
    <location file="backend/node_modules/node-gyp/CONTRIBUTING.md"/>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
